hello everyone thank you for joining so
大家好，谢谢您的加入
before we started I would like to ask a
在我们开始之前，我想问一个
couple of questions first who wasn't at
首先是几个问题，谁不在
the keynote on Tuesday wasn't
周二的主题演讲不是
wasn't okay that's good so and the
不好，所以很好
reason why I'm asking is this
我问的原因是这个
presentation is about so you've seen the
演示文稿是关于，所以您已经看到了
the live coding session on Tuesday
星期二的现场编码会议
really what what we wanted to show you
真的，我们想给你看什么
is how spring would improve the
春天将如何改善
developer experience so what we do what
开发人员的经验，所以我们做什么
we try to improve in every boot release
我们尝试在每个引导版本中进行改进
to help people being more productive and
帮助人们提高生产力，
this session is actually a follow-up to
本次会议实际上是对
that so in this session don't worry we
因此，在本次会议中，请不要担心我们
won't we do the keynote demonstrations
我们不会做主题演讲吗
actually a complete different app with
实际上是一个完整的不同应用
different well related and also
不同的相关性也好
different demos but we have a chance now
不同的演示，但我们现在有机会
with a 60 minute slot to go deeper and
有60分钟的时间可以深入了解
explain in more details what we couldn't
详细解释我们无法做到的
do during the keynote yeah and as well
在主题演讲期间也是如此
don't worry everything we're doing right
不用担心我们做的一切正确
now it's a repository on github in the
现在它是github中的存储库
spring one platform organization and get
成立一个平台组织并获得
up and all the commits are crafted with
起来，所有提交都是精心制作的
love so it's all explained you'll see
爱，这一切都说明你会看到
everything we're doing you'll see it so
我们正在做的所有事情，您都会看到它
don't worry and just sit back and enjoy
别担心，只是坐下来享受
and and don't is there to ask questions
而且不在那里问问题
during the presentation yeah we have
在演示过程中，我们有
time so do not hesitate to interrupt us
时间如此，请不要犹豫，打扰我们
so I'm with using spring boot already
所以我已经在使用Spring Boot
that's 50% ok so before we start this is
50％可以，所以在我们开始之前
live coding demo we'll have plenty of
现场编码演示，我们将有很多
slides first very boring so this is it
首先滑动很无聊，就是这样
ok so I have an app we have an app it's
好的，所以我有一个应用程序，有一个应用程序
a code for pepper sample application so
胡椒样本应用程序的代码，因此
the first thing we are going to do is to
我们要做的第一件事是
show you what that basic application
告诉你那个基本的应用程序
does so there is this own page you can
这样做有一个自己的页面，您可以
see some get up integration there you
看到一些起床整合
can actually submit a talk to the CFP ok
可以实际向CFP提交演讲
so you enter some data and yeah whatever
所以你输入一些数据，是的
and you submit what you get some
然后你提交你得到的一些
validation error then ok summary submit
验证错误，然后确定摘要提交
then oK you've talked has been submitted
那么你已经说过了，已经提交了
to the system
到系统
I can also see in the admin section
我也可以在管理部分看到
remember that because we'll go back
记住，因为我们会回去
several time there there's an admin
几次有一个管理员
section you can see if I'm trying to
部分，您可以查看我是否正在尝试
access that I need to log in so I'm
我需要登录才能访问，因此我
giving you the user password now admin
现在为您提供用户密码admin
admin 1 2 3
管理1 2 3
very clever and I'll have this page
非常聪明，我将显示此页面
where i can see the submitted proposals
在这里我可以看到提交的提案
because I'm using dev tools and we'll go
因为我正在使用开发工具，我们会去
back to that in a minute
再过一分钟
or almost I get sorry automatically a
或几乎我会自动对不起
sorry that's the other one I
抱歉，那是我的另一个
automatically get this nice h2 console
自动获得这个漂亮的H2控制台
feature so I'm using current table using
功能，所以我正在使用当前表
h2 so it's an in-memory database I will
h2，所以它是一个内存数据库
change that so every time the
每次改变
application starts we create the schema
应用程序启动，我们创建架构
hibernate quits the scheme automatically
休眠自动退出方案
for us and then we can have access to
为我们，然后我们就可以访问
today to the data that way so this is
今天这样的数据，这是
really our development environment for
确实我们的开发环境
look maybe other code now yeah I think
看起来现在可能还有其他代码是的，我认为
we also need to show you that we are
我们还需要向您展示我们
fetching some data from github and
从github获取一些数据，
because the github API is rate limited
因为github API受速率限制
so if you make to me request and you
因此，如果您向我提出要求，而您
don't have any authentication we'll get
没有任何认证，我们会得到
up at some point get up will say just
在某个时候起床会说
stop and we'll stop responding so for
停止，我们将停止响应，因此
that we have for now a get up token with
我们现在有一个起床令牌
an environment variable so we're not
一个环境变量，所以我们不是
really happy about this we'll don't
对此我们感到非常高兴，我们不会
really that out during doing our talk
真的在我们谈话期间
but just to let you know we're not stuck
但只是让您知道我们没有被卡住
with get up because we we have a token
起床，因为我们有令牌
right now to assure our requests against
现在确保我们的要求
the API so if you don't specify a token
API，所以如果您不指定令牌
when you call the github API you have a
当您调用github API时，
60 60 invocation per minute per hour
每分钟每小时60 60次调用
sorry rate limit so you can make up to
抱歉，您无法进行费率限制
60 calls to the github API per hour
每小时60次对github API的调用
which is really not a lot so what I did
真的不是很多，所以我做了
what I've done is I registered an
我所做的是我注册了
application token and then I'm injecting
应用程序令牌，然后注入
that as an environment variable so it's
作为环境变量，所以
using add value for now it's bad don't
现在使用增值是不好的
do it we will fix it the other thing
做到这一点，我们将修复另一件事
that we have in this application is
我们在此应用程序中拥有的是
basic security configuration where you
基本安全配置
can see
可以看到
all kinds of well the onion section you
各式各样的洋葱段你
need to have to have the onion roll and
需要有洋葱卷和
we are making the older static resources
我们正在使用较旧的静态资源
or application public so you don't need
或应用程序公开，因此您不需要
to be a fornicated to to see those and
见识那些
then same thing for a news page where
然后新闻页面也一样
you see the latest commits on the spring
您会在春天看到最新的提交
turmeric and on spring boot and we also
姜黄和 spring boot ，我们也
made the submit page public but we may
公开提交页面，但我们可能
change that in your future now we also
现在就改变您的未来
have our login page which is the thing
有我们的登录页面就是这样
that you've seen and yeah that's that's
你已经看到了，是的，那是
pretty much it so if you look at this
差不多，所以如果你看这个
application the spring bootie
应用春季短靴
application
应用
besides the security configure is really
除了安全配置真的
not much really
真的不多
if you look also at static assets down
如果您还看静态资产下降
there so you have all the templates
在那里，所以您拥有所有模板
that's using mustache using mr. Frye I
那是使用先生的胡子。弗莱一世
know
知道
timely time leaves are using time media
及时的休假正在使用时间媒体
and so that's for the templates
这是针对模板的
directory right there and the static
目录在那里，静态
directory is a common location for
目录是一个常见的位置
static assets so whenever you drop a
静态资产，因此每当您丢掉一个
file there we will serve it so you can
在那里归档，我们将为您服务
serve very easily CSS images and whatnot
可以非常轻松地提供CSS图像等
and springboard also support web job and
和跳板还支持网络作业，
in does that automatically for us now
现在自动为我们做
we're going to try to make that
我们将尝试使
application a bit better
应用好一点
and since we have dev tools though the
由于我们拥有开发工具
whole experience is is much much easier
整个体验要容易得多
and you'll see how so the first thing we
然后您会看到我们第一件事
need to do is to enable that live reload
需要做的是启用实时重载
thing that's what I've done at the
那是我在
keynote so maybe a bit of words about
主题演讲，所以也许有一些关于
that so a live reload live root server
这样一来，实时重新加载实时根服务器
and client we're not actually doing that
和客户，我们实际上并没有这样做
it's a third party company building that
这是一家第三方公司
product but the nice thing about it is
产品，但是关于它的好处是
the specification between the server and
服务器与
the client is open source and the client
客户端是开源的，客户端
they provide that browser plugin they do
他们提供的浏览器插件
so for chrome 5 for Firefox Internet
因此适用于Firefox 5的Chrome 5
Explorer and whatnot so you can install
资源管理器等什么都可以安装
that for free in the browser that you're
您在浏览器中免费获得的
using what we've done is we implemented
使用我们已经完成的工作
a very very very basic revolute server
一个非常非常基本的革命服务器
so when you start an app with dev tools
因此，当您使用开发工具启动应用程序时
it will also fire up a live reload
它也会触发实时重载
server and that's the reason why I am
服务器，这就是为什么我是
able to commit to connect sorry
能够承诺对不起
to the application so so so that library
到应用程序以便库
alert server is actually away from four
警报服务器实际上距离四个
dev tools right the first step for dev
开发工具是开发的第一步
tools it's actually a way for dev tools
工具，这实际上是开发工具的一种方式
to send a signal to your browser or your
向您的浏览器或您的设备发送信号
plugin here whenever something changed
每当有变化时在这里插件
in your application so that you don't
在您的应用程序中，这样您就不会
have to change something in your app
必须在您的应用程序中进行更改
then go back to your browser and then
然后回到浏览器，然后
refresh with that live reload signal
用实时重载信号刷新
whenever something changes the browser
每当改变浏览器
is made aware of that and it's reloading
意识到这一点，并且正在重新加载
the page as soon as it happens so that's
该页面一旦发生，那就是
one one thing you don't have to do
一件事，你不必做
during during development it's
在开发过程中
refreshing all the time so you get that
时刻刷新，让您明白
signal but how spring boot is guessing
信号，但 spring boot 如何猜测
when to sync that signal we will see
何时同步该信号，我们将看到
about say about that when we make
关于说，当我们做
changes to enter the application so
更改进入应用程序，以便
first thing about this app is we lack of
这个应用程式的第一件事是我们缺乏
inspiration there's some texture
灵感有些质感
probably should be changed so let's have
可能应该改变，所以让我们有
some kind of very nice you know slogan
某种非常好的口号你知道
share your patient is very nice so
分享你的病人非常好，所以
recompiling the application is doing
重新编译应用程序正在执行
something on spring boots and then
spring boot 上的东西，然后
sending a signal and refreshing your
发送信号并刷新您的
browser so that's one for another first
浏览器，因此首先
step was well for pradesh tools dev
对于Pradesh Tools开发人员而言，这一步很好
tools is automatically configuring
工具正在自动配置
defaults for your application in
您的应用程序的默认值
development mode so here for example
开发模式，例如这里
it's a it's a configuring time leaf not
这是一个配置时间，不是
to cache templates in development
在开发中缓存模板
otherwise you'd have to restart your
否则，您将不得不重新启动
application because the the a the
应用程序，因为
templates are compiled in cached so here
模板是在缓存中编译的，因此这里
they're not so you can you can refresh
他们不是，所以你可以刷新
the application and you see the changes
应用程序，您会看到更改
on your page and same thing for the
在您的页面上，对于
static resources by default dev tools
静态资源默认为开发工具
will tell the your browser that it
会告诉您的浏览器
shouldn't cache those resources because
不应该缓存那些资源，因为
you're probably changing those a lot
你可能会改变很多
during the development so that's not
在开发过程中，所以不是
very small per se because I mean if you
本身很小，因为我的意思是如果你
change a static asset and you disable
更改静态资产，然后禁用
the cache you could do that yourself I
缓存，你可以自己做
mean you have some code you have some
意思是你有一些代码，你有一些
configuration to write but it's not
配置写，但不是
really super smart right because you
真的超级聪明吧，因为你
changed some file you disabled the cache
更改了一些文件，您禁用了缓存
so if you hit the page again because the
因此，如果您再次点击该页面，因为
cache as as in the template it will be
像模板一样缓存
read again
再读一次
and you'll get that reflected
你会得到反映
automatically but devtool does more and
自动但devtool做更多
we can see here that there is a track
我们可以在这里看到一条轨道
missing for our CFP and there's a code
我们的CFP缺少，有一个代码
here that represent the track so I'm
在这里代表曲目，所以我
going to add one and we're going to add
要添加一个，我们要添加
web track so I'm changing Java code
网络跟踪，所以我要更改Java代码
basically and if I do that I have the
基本上，如果我这样做，我有
web track right there no so what happens
网络跟踪没有那里发生了什么
here is that dev tools is also adding a
这是开发工具还添加了一个
file watcher on your application so
您应用程序上的文件监视程序
whenever something file has been
每当有文件
modified by you in your application so
由您在您的应用程序中修改，因此
static resources or classes it's seeing
看到的静态资源或类
that doing whatever is necessary so for
做任何必要的事情
a class it's recompiling I mean your
一个正在重新编译的类，我的意思是你
recompile the project so it's restarting
重新编译项目，以便重新启动
the boot application just the spring
引导应用程序只是春天
context actually and refreshing your
实际情况并刷新您的
browser with a signal so the trick here
浏览器有信号，所以这里的窍门
is that spring boot one in development
那是 spring boot 在开发中吗
mode with dev tools spring mood is using
开发人员工具的春天模式正在使用
two dev tools is using to two different
两个开发工具正在使用两个不同的
class loaders one with all your
一流的装载机
dependencies so everything you've added
依赖项，因此您添加的所有内容
in your pond XML or your build up Gradle
在您的池塘XML或您构建的Gradle中
those tend to change not as much as
那些变化不大
everything else which are your study
你所学的其他一切
resources and your code which live in a
资源和您的代码
different class loader so whenever
不同的类加载器，因此无论何时
something happens when you're with your
当你和你在一起时，会发生一些事情
code for example boot detects that
例如代码引导检测到
throws away that class loader creates a
扔掉那个类加载器创建一个
new one and restart the spring context
新的并重新启动spring上下文
and that's actually pretty fast because
这实际上非常快，因为
when you start your application starting
当您启动应用程序时
the JVM warming up and loading all the
JVM预热并加载所有
classes from your dependencies that
来自您的依赖项的类
takes a lot a lot of time and restarting
需要很多时间然后重新启动
the spring context it's actually pretty
春天的背景实际上很漂亮
fast so in that example that's what
快速，所以在那个例子中
exactly what we're doing when we were
正是我们在做什么的时候
changing the code so um so you've seen
如此更改代码，您已经看到了
two the two main use cases of dev tools
两个dev工具的两个主要用例
really is one the first one is we've
真的是第一个，我们已经
changed something that does not require
改变了不需要的东西
the context restart you don't need to
上下文重新启动，您不需要
restore the context if you change a
如果您更改了上下文，则还原上下文
template right and the case where you
模板权利以及您的情况
change some code so obviously we don't
更改一些代码，所以显然我们不会
know the impact of changing that code so
知道更改代码的影响，因此
we
我们
drop the class order we create a new one
删除班级顺序，我们创建一个新的
and restart the application you can
并重新启动应用程序，您可以
teach to bring boot about that stuff so
教带来东西的引导
if you have a location where not Java
如果您的位置不是Java
code obviously you could do so but that
代码显然可以，但是
would probably be nasty but if you have
可能很讨厌，但如果您有
places in your app resources that do not
在您的应用资源中
require the application to be restarted
要求重新启动应用程序
or on the other hand you have some
或者另一方面，你有一些
specific area when you change some some
当您更改一些特定区域
config file for instance and it requires
例如配置文件，它需要
the application to restart you can teach
重新启动应用程序，您可以教
the dev tool to actually change those
开发工具来真正改变那些
behavior you can also teach dev tools to
您还可以教开发人员工具
watch files outside of your project so
监视项目外部的文件，以便
for instance if you have a client-side
例如，如果您有客户端
application using angular or whatever
使用角度或其他方式的应用程序
and you serving your serving static
而您的服务静态
resources from an external module you
来自外部模块的资源
can actually tell dev tools go watch
可以告诉开发人员去观看
those files and whenever you change code
这些文件，以及每当您更改代码时
of your client the browser will refresh
您的客户端的浏览器将刷新
all the application might restart if
如果以下所有应用程序可能会重新启动
that's what you want but dev tools has
这就是您想要的，但是开发工具具有
been there for since one three right and
自从三分之一以来一直在那里
now we're going to show you also new
现在我们将向您展示新的
features with dev tools and how it works
开发工具的功能及其工作方式
right so we have one one tiny problem
对，所以我们有一个小问题
again it's the same thing so I'm going
再次是同一件事，所以我要去
to do that really quick you've seen that
快速地做到这一点，您已经看到了
at the keynote I don't have an error
在主题演讲中我没有错误
page for that so I'm going to just
的页面，所以我将只
create one so it's yet another use case
创建一个，这是另一个用例
of dev tools is you add new stuff to
开发工具是您向其中添加新内容
your app and because you do will detect
您的应用程序，因为您确实会检测到
that but this time you're creating that
但是这次您要创建一个
into the templates templates folder
进入模板模板文件夹
during the keynote it was a static file
在主题演讲中，这是一个静态文件
in static now it's a it's actually a
在静态中，这实际上是一个
real finally template so we will see
真正的最终模板，所以我们将看到
later how we can benefit from the fact
以后我们如何从事实中受益
it's a template so this app has one
这是一个模板，所以这个应用程序有一个
major issue and the major issue it has
主要问题及其主要问题
is anybody can actually submit one two
任何人都可以实际提交一两个
you can say you can provide any
你可以说你可以提供任何
information you want there and if you
您想要在那里的信息，如果您
submit several talks you have to repeat
提交一些您必须重复的演讲
your information over and over again
您的信息一遍又一遍
which is about right so we thought maybe
这是正确的，所以我们认为也许
we should find a way to add some kind of
我们应该找到一种方法来添加某种
authentication to this app
验证此应用
and if you want to do that usually you
如果你想这样做，通常
need to create I mean yeah you have to
需要创建我的意思是，你必须
computer security you have to create a
您必须创建一个计算机安全
database for that I have to register
我必须注册的数据库
your users and like I forgot my password
您的用户，就像我忘记了密码
form etcetera you have to do all that or
表格等你必须做的所有
you can rely on a third party
你可以依靠第三方
application or service to do the Africa
申请或服务到非洲
of application in one which is actually
应用程序实际上是
really nice is to so off to is about
真的很好是这样
authorization but if you use it in a
授权，但如果您在
different way you can also use it as a
您也可以将其用作另一种方式
single sign-on service and that's what
单一登录服务，就是这样
we're actually doing right now so the
我们实际上现在正在做，所以
next demo is about to enable single
下一个演示即将启用单
sign-on with OAuth and we need to find a
使用OAuth登录，我们需要找到一个
provider and well since it's a
提供者，而且因为它是一个
conference it's probably about code
会议可能与代码有关
github might be a good option for that
github可能是个不错的选择
you probably have already have a github
您可能已经有一个github
account so this is a new feature in one
帐户，因此这是一项新功能
for to you you'll see how you can
为您服务，您将看到如何
computer a nod to provider as a single
电脑向供应商致敬
sign-on in your build application so
在您的构建应用程序中登录，以便
you're actually you actually need a new
实际上，您实际上需要一个新的
dependency you'll need here security or
依赖，您将需要在这里安全或
two then as a I want to enable OS so
然后两个作为我要启用操作系统
single sign-on for both if I do that I'm
如果我这样做，那么两者都可以单点登录
basically telling spring boot please
基本上告诉 spring boot
instead of the instead of the
而不是代替
traditional login form just create a
传统的登录表单只需创建一个
login logout interceptor for me so
为我登录注销拦截器
because I'm doing this I actually don't
因为我这样做我实际上不
need the formula gang anymore that can
需要配方帮派了
go away and very important now we want
走开，非常重要，现在我们要
to make sure that whenever you access
确保您每次访问
submit you have to login right so
提交您必须登录正确，所以
currently submit is permit all if I
目前提交的是允许所有，如果我
remove that I'll go to the next rule
删除，我将转到下一条规则
which means okay you need to you need to
这意味着好吧，您需要
be on tour to date it so now we need to
参加巡回演出，所以现在我们需要
change our application so that we
更改我们的应用程序，以便我们
actually ask get up for your credit for
实际要求起床
your right and your credentials
您的权利和凭证
information
信息
but if you've ever worked with oauth2
但是，如果您曾经使用过oauth2
you know that you need some kind of
你知道你需要某种
other information information on the
关于其他信息
Elan to providers like URLs where you
向供应商那样的Elan宣传
should wear your auth clients should who
应该穿你的认证客户应该谁
you're having should talk to the server
您应该与服务器对话
so that's the configuration we are
这就是我们的配置
adding here so the access token
在此处添加访问令牌
endpoints etc etc so that's the read the
端点等，所以这是读
full properties that you need to teach
您需要教的完整属性
spring boot to which to which you're
你要去的 spring boot
right needs to contact to do this
正确需要联系才能做到这一点
identification process you'll find these
识别过程中，您会发现这些
four properties whatever the O's
四个属性，无论O是什么
provider you're using if you want to use
您要使用的提供程序
Twitter for instance or Google or
例如Twitter或Google或
whatever oath resource provider
任何宣誓资源提供者
available the only thing that is going
唯一会发生的事情
to change is those URI and if you go on
要更改的是那些URI，如果继续
the Developer area for instance the
开发人员区域，例如
developer network for Twitter you'll
Twitter开发人员网络
easily find the UI that you have to use
轻松找到您必须使用的UI
and we're actually almost there we only
实际上我们几乎就在那里
need now our client ID and secret our
现在需要我们的客户ID并秘密
client secret so I'm really what's going
客户秘密，所以我真的是怎么回事
to happen is you're going to be
发生的是你将要
redirected to github and get up will say
重定向到github并起床会说
there is this app that wants to know
有这个程序想知道
about you do you agree then if you say
关于你，你同意吗，如果你说
yes then you give us a right to actually
是的，那么你给我们权利
see all you are and we reassure so
看到你的一切，我们保证
basically that there is a definite
基本上有一个确定的
change so data gives us back basically
变化，因此数据基本上可以将我们带回
some information about you and to get
有关您的一些信息并获得
the client ID and client secret we need
我们需要的客户ID和客户机密
to register our application with github
用github注册我们的应用程序
and that's what we're about to do
这就是我们要做的
against the spring one platform Oregon
抵制春季俄勒冈州的一个平台
get up that's where the actual code
站起来就是实际的代码
lives actually the CFP - example
实际上住在CFP中-示例
application is the right repository you
应用程序是您正确的存储库
need to be admin to the organization to
需要成为该组织的管理员才能
see this so if you have a github account
看到这个，如果你有一个github帐号
just go on to your own repository the
只需转到您自己的存储库
repository with you use you username
与您一起使用的存储库用户名
you'll find this settings page their iOS
您会在其iOS的此设置页面中找到
application then you just register an
应用程序，然后您只需注册一个
application you call that C if PA
如果您将PA称为C
for instance the on page is the thing
例如页面上的东西
basically where DTaP will call you so
基本上DTaP会打电话给您
when when you log in your spring boot
当您登录Spring Boot时
application with on the four properties
具有四个属性的应用程序
it will use the first URI to contact
它将使用第一个URI进行联系
data but say okay I need to exchange
数据，但可以，我需要交换
with that guy
和那个家伙
that person and once the authentication
那个人，一旦认证
process has complete get up we basically
过程已经完成，我们基本上
were direct to the to the Euro right
直接指向欧元区
that has been said there so because I'm
在那里有人说，因为我
going to show you the client ID and
将向您显示客户ID和
client secret which I'm not supposed to
我不应该的客户机密
I'm going to say that it is redirect to
我要说的是它被重定向到
this and while there's not much you can
这个虽然没有多少你可以
do with that right so you need to
做到这一点，所以你需要
provide some information about the
提供有关
application so that people actually know
应用程序，使人们真正知道
why they should say ok and once I've
为什么他们应该说好的，一旦我
done that I had the client ID occur in
完成我的客户端ID发生在
secret so I can go back here where I had
秘密，所以我可以回到这里
my security users actually useless now
我的安全用户现在实际上已经没用了
and use client ID instead so that's the
并使用客户端ID代替
last step really and client secret so
最后一步真的和客户的秘密如此
we've added the dependency one
我们添加了一个依赖项
annotation some configuration in our
注释我们的一些配置
files
档案
we've tweet our security config and now
我们已经发布了安全配置，现在
we'll see if everything works so now
我们现在看看是否一切正常
when we access a protected page we
当我们访问受保护的页面时，我们
should see the OAuth authentication page
应该看到OAuth身份验证页面
from github so I can still access the
从github上，所以我仍然可以访问
own page because there is nothing that
自己的页面，因为没有什么
prevents me to do that right now
阻止我现在这样做
but if I click Submit now I go back on
但是如果单击立即提交，我会继续
github and get up tells me there is the
github起来告诉我有
CFG example that wants to access your
想要访问您的CFG示例
account he wants to read public data
他想读取公共数据的帐户
only so that's also something you can
只是这样你也可以
change you can also specify scopes you
更改您还可以指定范围
could say I want to be able to access
可以说我希望能够访问
that part of the user profile and that
用户个人资料的一部分，以及
will be displayed that that will be
将显示那将是
displayed locked down there but right
显示锁定在那里，但右边
now all I need is I need your name
现在我需要的是你的名字
that's all I need for my for my purpose
这就是我为我所需要的
I could have said I want to access your
我本可以说我想访问您的
email even even if you if you don't have
即使您没有也可以发送电子邮件
a pubic email you have
您拥有的公开电子邮件
mainly new accountant it's not visible
主要是新会计师，它不可见
to the user then there is a special
给用户，那么有一个特殊的
scope in github to actually have access
github中的范围实际上可以访问
to that
那个
so the question is what do you have to
所以问题是你要做什么
add as dependencies to actually make
添加为实际依赖项
that stuff work and he answers this part
东西起作用，他回答了这一部分
of the support is inside spring security
支持的是弹簧安全性
or off and part of the enable Oh after
或关闭，部分启用之后
SSO is in spring boot itself so it's a
SSO本身在 spring boot 中，因此
standard protocol that you configure
您配置的标准协议
right so there's no spring security or
对，所以没有弹簧安全性或
o'the Boogle spring security or o'the
BoogleSpring Security 性或其他
Twitter there is no such thing because
Twitter没有这样的事情，因为
it's it's simply the OAuth protocol and
这只是OAuth协议，
you're just configuring which service
您只是在配置哪个服务
needs to be contacted right so I'm going
需要正确联系，所以我要去
to say okay and I'm on to automatically
说好吧，我会自动
redirected to that and you can see right
重定向到那个，你可以看到正确的
there actually I'm logged in now okay
那里实际上我现在已经登录好了
there's a problem though I still I still
有一个问题，尽管我仍然
have the email in the name fields there
在名称字段中有电子邮件
we are going to remove that in soon but
我们将很快删除它，但是
one problem we have now with this you're
我们现在遇到的一个问题是
not allowed to go to the admin page
不允许进入管理页面
anymore because right now before we were
因为在我们之前
admin when we had our previous security
当我们有以前的安全性时的管理员
configuration and now we need to do
配置，现在我们需要做
something to actually decide who is can
真正决定谁可以的东西
be an admin user who can have that admin
成为可以拥有该管理员的管理员用户
role in our application so what we had
在我们的应用程序中扮演的角色
before was playing spring security so
之前是在打Spring Security 赛，所以
the default setup that boot provides and
引导提供的默认设置，以及
you see in the security username admin
您在安全用户名admin中看到
security password admin one two three
安全密码管理员一二三
by default that's in the dock by default
默认情况下，它位于扩展坞中
we will create a user with role admin so
我们将创建一个角色为admin的用户，以便
that's what we got when we initially
这就是我们最初得到的
started right now we have no rules we
现在开始，我们没有规则，
just plain I'm just a plain getup user
只是普通我只是普通用户
like thank you so there is nothing that
像谢谢你，所以没有什么
tells I'm actually an admin in this
告诉我我实际上是管理员
system so we're going to change that so
系统，因此我们将对其进行更改
whenever someone is a fun occasion
每当有人有趣的时候
against our application we need to hook
针对我们的应用程序，我们需要挂钩
into that point and extract authorities
进入这一点并提取权威
from those people to know
从那些人知道
they're allowed to have that role or
他们被允许担任那个角色，或者
this role and that's what we need to do
这个角色，这就是我们需要做的
right now so first we can decide who can
现在，所以首先我们可以决定谁可以
be an admin and for now we'll do that
成为管理员，现在我们将做
statically with just the list of our get
仅与我们获取的列表静态关联
up handles and we can add something to
手柄，我们可以添加一些东西
our security configuration that says
我们的安全配置说
that fetches the login part of the user
获取用户的登录部分
information we fetch from get up check
我们从起床检查中获取的信息
if that username is in our special list
如果该用户名在我们的特殊列表中
and if it is then we are adding the
如果是，那么我们要添加
admin role for that person and that's
该人的管理员角色，这是
what we actually do so that that
我们实际上所做的是
callback is is basically the OAuth
回调基本上是OAuth
provider that you've chosen is going to
您选择的提供者将
send us back some information some
给我们发一些信息
unstructured information in the case of
在以下情况下的非结构化信息
github there is a log in key that's
github上有一个登录键
actually your github account you'll get
实际上，您将获得github帐户
of ID so we'll use that to see if it's
ID，因此我们将使用它来查看
contained within that list and if that's
包含在该列表中，如果
the case then we change the user right
在这种情况下，我们更改用户权限
if I do that I'm an admin again
如果我这样做，我将再次成为管理员
okay but it's a bit I mean having that
好的，但这是我的意思
in a static list it's a bit like not
在静态列表中，有点像不是
great in our application we can
我们的应用程序很棒
definitely improve that so what we not
肯定会改善，所以我们没有
what we want to show you now is how you
我们现在想告诉你的是你如何
can use print booth to use to expose
可以使用印刷棚来曝光
configuration properties for your app so
应用的配置属性
you've seen that at the keynote there
您已经在主题演讲中看到了
was already some kind of infrastructure
已经是某种基础设施
set up and this nice content assistance
设置和这个不错的内容帮助
and blah blah blah so you probably
等等等等，所以你可能
wonder now what does it take to include
现在想知道包括什么
that in your app from scratch and that's
从头开始在您的应用中
what we're going to show you so the
我们将向您展示的内容
first thing that you need to do really
您真正要做的第一件事
is to have a representation of those
是要代表那些
keys as as an object structure so I'm
键作为对象结构，所以我
going to create that for you right now
现在就为您创建
very quick so as long as it looks like a
只要看起来像
Java bin and it's properly documented
Java bin，并且已正确记录
just like this you're good to go
就像这样，你很好
and you can even nest several inner
你甚至可以嵌套几个内部
classes to structure your your namespace
类来构造您的名称空间
and that's perfectly fine so the the key
那很好，所以关键
here is if you want to have nested
这是如果您想嵌套
namespace so you could have separate
命名空间，所以你可以有单独的
classes of course but if you want to
课程，当然，但如果您想
gather a certain concept and have some
收集某个概念并有一些
kind of nested key so food dot something
一种嵌套的键，所以食物点了点东西
dot something the keys to create a POJO
点一些键来创建一个POJO
in the POJO URL right now you can see
现在在POJO URL中，您可以看到
that it this is this definer static in
这是这个定义器静态
your classes the reason why it's done
您的课程完成的原因
that way is because the metadata will be
那是因为元数据将是
picked up automatically I'll show you
自动接我给你看
that in a minute and the thing that
一分钟内，那件事
matters is the name of the property so
重要的是财产的名称，所以
if you have a debt getter property it
如果您有债务获取者财产
means you'll get a get app namespace
意味着您将获得一个get应用程序名称空间
security namespace in this case yeah and
安全命名空间在这种情况下是的，
we need a way to namespace this actual
我们需要一种对实际名称空间进行命名的方法
those all those keys and for that we
这些键，为此，我们
need the add configuration properties
需要添加配置属性
annotation and we say that let's say we
注解，我们说我们
want to namespace the whole class under
想要命名整个类的名称
CFP and so we'll get CF p dot github etc
CFP，所以我们将获得CF p点github等
etcetera so basically that class exposed
基本上是这样
to proper
适当地
geez now cfp get up the token and CF p
geez现在cfp获取令牌和CF p
dot security that admins okay so I want
点安全管理员可以，所以我想要
to use that and this class this the only
使用这个，这是唯一的
purpose of this class is to bound to
此类的目的是为了
bind the environment to bind bind some
绑定环境，绑定一些
configuration key from the environment
来自环境的配置密钥
to your class so you can actually inject
上课，所以你实际上可以注入
that as pretty much anything in spring
春天几乎没有
so I'm going to show you that let's see
所以我要告诉你，让我们看看
I can go right there and say okay I want
我可以去那里说我想要
to inject safety properties and I can
注入安全性能，我可以
say a property is yet
说财产还没有
security get admins and remove that
安全获取管理员并将其删除
thing but IntelliJ complains here tells
事情，但IntelliJ抱怨这里告诉
me that's not a bean I don't know about
我不是我不知道的beans
that stuff and it's actually very right
这些东西，实际上是非常正确的
if you look here it's not a metallic
如果你看这里不是金属的
asian it's not a component it's not
亚洲这不是一个组成部分，不是
going to be scanned by a components can
将由组件扫描
we did that on very purpose because we
我们这样做是有目的的，因为我们
want you to make sure that this object
希望您确保该对象
does not become like a complex object
不像一个复杂的对象
with bean dependency with with complex
与豆依赖与复杂
business logic the only purpose of that
业务逻辑的唯一目的
thing is to bind to the environment and
事情是要绑定到环境，
to provide added values on top of the
提供附加价值
environment so to make to really make
这样才能真正做到
that very clear I'm going to you can
很清楚，我要去找你
obviously add add component if you want
如果需要，显然添加添加组件
if that's what you want you can do that
如果那是您想要的，您可以这样做
and it will work but I'm just going to
它会工作，但我只是要
show you another way to do it I'm going
向您展示另一种方法，我要去
to say please process that class and if
说请处理该课，如果
I do that and I go back I have a bean
我这样做，回去我有一个豆
now the other thing that we want to do
现在我们要做的另一件事
is we want to
我们想要
remove that crap and use our CSV
删除该废话，并使用我们的CSV
properties instead so let's do this so
属性，所以让我们这样做
you can see that the value currently
您可以看到当前的值
that we bind to a CFP underscored it up
我们绑定到CFP上就突出了这一点
and ESCO token in uppercase but it
和ESCO令牌为大写字母，但它
doesn't matter because with a good
没关系，因为有了一个好
relaxed binding there are actual
放松约束力有实际
conventions to deal with it
处理它的惯例
so the underscores and capital letters
下划线和大写字母
they map easily to what we've actually
他们很容易地映射到我们实际
done so spring boot really binds to
做到了， spring boot 真的绑定到
system properties environment variables
系统属性环境变量
command line switch step that you put in
您输入的命令行切换步骤
the application properties in Yemen so
也门的应用程序属性
there's plenty of ways you can customize
有很多方法可以自定义
your configuration and as brandriss said
您的配置和如brandriss所说
we have some kind of relaxed way of
我们有某种轻松的方式
binding those values because typically
绑定这些值，因为通常
OS environment variables requires you
操作系统环境变量要求您
and certain OS the property needs to be
和某些操作系统，该属性需要
in uppercase and you can use dots you
大写，你可以使用点
use dots on certain OS it will just look
在某些操作系统上使用点，它将看起来
work so we take care of that I mean are
工作，所以我们照顾好我的意思是
in your other file I've seen that you've
在您的其他文件中，我看到您已经
got that red banner on top right is that
在右上方有红色横幅是
an error so yeah the next step is
一个错误，所以下一步是
actually how do we how do we have
实际上我们如何拥有
content assistance for that stuff right
对该内容的内容帮助
how do you how do you do you get the
你如何你如何得到
list of keys
键列表
well IntelliJ wants us that the
IntelliJ希望我们
annotation processor is not enabled so
注释处理器未启用，因此
let's add that and explain should
让我们添加一下并解释一下
quickly explain you what it does because
快速向您解释它的作用，因为
if you try if we try right now to write
如果您尝试，如果我们现在尝试写
those keys down in our configuration we
这些按键在我们的配置中
won't have the autocomplete support and
将不具有自动完成功能支持，并且
we actually need that to get this so if
我们实际上需要得到它，所以如果
I'm adding this I'm basically adding a
我要添加这个，我基本上要添加一个
new that's why it's optional right there
这就是为什么它在那里是可选的
I'm adding a new component that the
我要添加一个新组件
compiler will detect so the annotation
编译器将检测到该注释
processor is a
处理器是一个
completed standard and this
完成标准和本
implementation is basically going to
实施基本上将
inspect your code the code in your
检查您的代码中的代码
project fine configuration properties
项目精细配置属性
object and generate some metadata for it
对象并为其生成一些元数据
so this would be quite transparent for
所以这对于
you basically and once you've done that
基本上，一旦完成，
if that works properly I check define
如果可以正常工作，我检查定义
okay it was generated for the class
好的，它是为课程生成的
issue then you get this right
问题，那么你正确了
you can see also that you get the
你也可以看到你得到了
documentation so the documentation is
文档，所以文档是
actually extracted from here you can
实际上是从这里提取的
also provide default values you can
还提供默认值，您可以
provide metadata for value so the plenty
提供价值的元数据，所以大量
of things you can do so this is really a
您可以做的事情实际上是
good mechanism if you want to provide
如果您想提供良好的机制
added value for your own configuration
为您自己的配置增加价值
keys so let's play with that a bit and
键，让我们一起玩
let's say I'm not a nun mean anymore
假设我不再是修女
just to show you it works go back to the
只是为了向您展示它的工作原理，
application yeah when you're trying to
是的，当您尝试
access the admin page you're not allowed
访问您不允许的管理页面
anymore to access that page because I'm
不再访问该页面，因为我
not in any right anymore so um one thing
再也没有了，所以一件事
we want to do at this point is maybe to
我们现在想做的也许是
have a narrow page for the fall 3 yeah
秋季3的页面很窄
so we probably need to duplicate the
所以我们可能需要复制
other one name it for 3 dot HTML right
另一个用3点HTML命名
or we could have something more clever
否则我们可能会更聪明
so it could be we could be most part
所以可能是我们可以成为大多数人
about it we have a page for 404 we want
关于它，我们有一个想要的404页面
a page for 403 and for our own purpose a
403页，供我们使用
single page would work so what you can
单页将工作，所以你可以
do is bring boot now is you can just
现在要做的就是启动，您可以
need that for xx and if you do this we
需要用于xx，如果您这样做，我们
will recognize a pattern and we will
会认出一个模式，我们会
serve serve it so if you have a fall
服务它，所以如果你跌倒
fall on top will take the fall for top
跌倒在顶部会跌倒在顶部
but if there is no client-side error
但是如果没有客户端错误
page defined then we will take the
定义的页面，然后我们将
default if there's one but it's still
如果有一个则默认，但仍然
called not found so we still have a
找不到，所以我们还有一个
problem it so yeah it still it's the
问题，是的，仍然是
wrong so let's show you why it's a
错误的，让我们向您展示为什么它是
template and why it's actually
模板及其实际原因
interesting for your use case so I'm
对您的用例很有趣，所以我
going to use
将要使用
here I'm going to say oops + error there
在这里我要说oops + error
is a problem with the quotes and
是引号和
single-single towards a good point and
单向一个好点，并且
the error we're actually given an error
错误，我们实际上得到了一个错误
object by the by boot when there are
通过引导时对象
occurs so you can use that object into
发生，所以您可以使用该对象
your template to do whatever you need n
您的模板可以做您所需的任何事情n
in our case we are using that - in the
在我们的情况下，我们正在使用-
title - to customize the page so if you
title-自定义页面，因此，如果您
look at the dot you will see that the
看点，您会看到
spring but--will will have an error
春天，但是-将有一个错误
attributes Bojo that it's going to give
赋予它的Bojo属性
you out of the box you can customize
开箱即用，您可以自定义
that so you'll get the error you'll get
这样你会得到错误，你会得到
the status code you'll get the stack
您将获得堆栈的状态码
trace if there's one you'll get the
追踪是否有一个你会得到
timestamp I think there's a few more
时间戳，我认为还有更多
account remember but it's in the dot
帐户记住，但是在点中
so all these of course you can use that
所以这些当然你可以用
in your own template okay now we have
在您自己的模板中，现在我们有了
the authentication but we still wanted
身份验证，但我们仍然想要
to use that for the submit page write
用它来提交页面
values you your authenticated but you
重视您的身份验证，但您
kind of need to still fill in the form
还是需要填写表格
with your email and your name etc where
与您的电子邮件和您的姓名等一起
we could easily derive that from your
我们可以很容易地从您那里得出
from your user information we've got
从您的用户信息中我们得到了
already so the next step really is to
已经如此，下一步真的是
actually use the information we get from
实际使用我们从中获得的信息
github what the gos provider really and
github gos提供者真正和什么
link that to your submission so there's
链接到您的提交，所以有
quite a lot of code so like Brian
很多代码，例如Br​​ian
explained we have this nice commit I'm
解释说我们有一个不错的承诺
going to not do live coding for this one
不会为此做现场编码
sorry what we've done with that commit
抱歉，我们已经完成了该提交
we've added a a user domain object to
我们向其中添加了一个用户域对象
persist in our database that user holds
保留在用户拥有的数据库中
all the information about our users when
有关用户的所有信息，何时
you're logged in we've also tweaked the
您已登录，我们还对
template to remove the email the email
用于删除电子邮件的模板
part of the form and we also change a
表格的一部分，我们还更改了
bit the header so you can get your your
咬一下标题，这样您就可以得到您的
picture from get up
从起床图片
you're logged in so with all that you
您已登录，因此拥有所有
have a much better experience when
有更好的经验时
you're logged in you don't need to fill
您已经登录，无需填写
in the old information you got your
在旧信息中，您得到了
picture on top and and if you submit
图片放在顶部，如果您提交
several things they're all linked to the
他们都关联了几件事
same person view and you can see that
同一个人的视图，您可以看到
into the the actual database we've got a
到实际的数据库中，我们有一个
new new table user you should know that
新的新表用户，您应该知道
we've also done something in our
我们也做了一些事情
security configuration when someone logs
有人登录时的安全性配置
in for the first time we're actually
第一次进入
creating the the user in in the database
在数据库中创建用户
so that we're sure that the user is
这样我们可以确定用户是
persisted before it can the person can
坚持不懈的人可以
create a new yeah and use a mission so
创建一个新的，并使用任务，所以
let's let's quickly show that first of
让我们快速展示一下
all what with what we've added is this
我们添加的全部就是这个
principal extractor yeah so basically
是主要提取者，所以基本上
what we want to do is we won't teach
我们想做的是我们不会教
spring security what the object
Spring Security 的对象是什么
representing the authenticator
代表认证者
authenticated user is so for that we we
经过身份验证的用户对我们来说
implement that interface again we get
再次实现该接口，我们得到
some information from the oath provider
宣誓提供者的一些信息
we use our service to ask it up please
我们使用我们的服务来询问它
give me more information about that user
给我有关该用户的更多信息
because that thing is actually actually
因为那东西实际上是
knows about the oath context if there is
知道宣誓的背景，如果有
scope attached to if there is scope
是否有范围
attached to the authentication process
附加到身份验证过程
you'll be able to access those
您将能够访问那些
information so the call that you're
信息，所以您的电话
going to make to get up will will match
要起床会匹配
the scope that you've asked as you've
您所要求的范围
seen I just asked for the public scope
看到我只是要求公开范围
so really doesn't change doesn't make
所以真的没有改变不会使
any difference but this thing is
没什么区别，但是这个东西是
actually pretty much transparent for you
实际上对你来说是透明的
now and if you do that instead of
现在，如果您这样做，而不是
getting the authentication principle all
全部获得认证原则
over the place in your application and
在您的应用程序中
you just have the username information
您只有用户名信息
from there you can actually customize
从那里你实际上可以自定义
the the type you'll get when you inject
注入时将得到的类型
that when you inject that Oliver unit
当您注入该Oliver装置时
application and then you can add more
应用程序，然后您可以添加更多
information
信息
in our case we've added many information
在我们的案例中，我们添加了许多信息
into that user object the the URL and of
该用户对象的网址和
the picture anything anything you'd like
图片任何你想要的
and that's the actual thing you can
那就是你可以做的真实的事情
inject here in the controller with
在这里注入控制器
annotated our controller argument with
注释了我们的控制器参数
the authentication principle and we've
认证原则，我们已经
added the type directive that we want
添加了我们想要的类型指令
and that's the type we will configure in
这就是我们将在其中配置的类型
our communication instructor so you can
我们的沟通指导老师
get the user your custom user object
获取用户您的自定义用户对象
wherever you want into the application
您想在哪里进入应用程序
meaning the controller but even in
意味着控制器，但即使在
templates right it's also the time with
模板，这也是时候
templates in the layout if you look at
如果您查看布局中的模板
the layout where we you have the name in
您在其中拥有名称的布局
the little picture on top then with here
上面的小图片然后放在这里
we're using a time with extension the
我们正在使用扩展时间
spring security extension so you can
Spring Security 扩展，因此您可以
directly use the authentication
直接使用身份验证
principle into your templates to get the
原理进入模板以获取
get up username or the URL of the
起床的用户名或网址
profile etc
个人资料等
okay so you'd like to okay
好的，所以你想好的
so you'd like to see that part again
所以你想再次看到那部分
where we get the information from the
我们从哪里获得信息
client so the information we got from
客户，所以我们从中获得的信息
the github API when we request an a
当我们请求一个github API时
request to the user endpoint of get up
请求起床的用户端点
that sends back all the information
发送回所有信息
about our user the login and other
关于我们的用户的登录名和其他
things and we are creating from there
事物，我们从那里开始创造
extracting the extracting the log in and
提取提取登录并
then we're creating from there our own
然后我们从那里创建我们自己的
user object and we are adding
用户对象，我们正在添加
information to that user and persisting
给该用户的信息并持续存在
it into the database so if you if you
它进入数据库，所以如果你
log in for the first time what what what
第一次登录什么什么什么
going to what's going to happen is we
即将发生的事情是我们
are going to actually create a user in
将实际在中创建用户
the system in the database to associate
数据库中要关联的系统
basically your submission to that user
基本上，您向该用户提交的内容
and if you log in maybe ten hours later
如果您大概十小时后登录
your user will still be in the system so
您的用户仍将在系统中，因此
we'll just use that and return that as
我们将使用它并返回为
the principle you can change that if
你可以改变的原则是
you're using Twitter or Google as a
您将Twitter或Google用作
north provider you can tweak the keys
北方供应商，您可以调整钥匙
extract more information use your own
提取更多信息，使用自己的
user object and do as much as you want
用户对象，随心所欲
so in our app will me have one on
所以在我们的应用程序中，我可以打开一个
dedication mechanism we could perfect
我们可以完善的奉献机制
they have two buttons one for get up one
他们有两个按钮，一个起床
for Twitter and depending on which one
对于Twitter，并取决于哪个
has been involved basically have a
已经参与基本上有一个
different call back and do different
不同的回叫，做不同的事情
things okay right our application is
没事吧，我们的应用程序是
pretty complete but I think we still
相当完整，但我认为我们仍然
have a problem with the rate limiting
速率限制有问题
because we're actually making a lot of
因为我们实际上做了很多
requests to get up we're making requests
要求起床，我们正在提出要求
when people wanna gate we're making
当人们想要登机时
requests when we are getting the the
请求，当我们得到
latest commits for spring for American
《美国之春》的最新承诺
Spring boots and that tends to make a
spring boot ，这往往使
lot of requests right now we told you
现在我们告诉你很多要求
we've got a token an authentication
我们有一个令牌进行身份验证
token to to make requests to the github
向github发出请求的令牌
API
API
not be forbidden to do so when we when
当我们什么时候不被禁止这样做
the rate-limiting is a is a we explode
限速是一个我们爆炸
that rate-limiting
那个限速
so right now Stefan is showing a way to
所以现在Stefan正在展示一种方法
he's requesting the the github API and
他正在请求github API和
extracting the rate-limiting information
提取限速信息
so we know that we have four four
所以我们知道我们有四个四个
thousand nine hundred remaining requests
剩余的一千九百个请求
and as long as we make we feather when
只要我们让我们羽毛
we refresh the page you can see that the
我们刷新页面，您可以看到
number of requests is slowly slowly but
请求数缓慢缓慢，但
surely is less line nice so you remember
当然，线条不太好，所以您还记得
that we did this caching thing at the
我们在
keynote to show you how you can enable
主题演讲，向您展示如何启用
caching something I'm not going to to
缓存我不打算去的东西
code that right now to save some time
立即进行编码以节省一些时间
for the rest of the demos I'm just going
对于其余的演示，我将继续
to check out that and just show you a
检查一下，然后给你看一个
different way of doing it so in in this
这样做的不同方式
app what I've decided to use was not to
我决定使用的应用程序不是
use caffeine just to show you a
使用咖啡因只是为了向您展示
different one so I'm going th cache in
不同的，所以我要缓存
each cache three and I'm using J cache
每个缓存三个，而我正在使用J缓存
the J cache API so the JSON of sevens
J缓存API，所以七人制的JSON
back and just to show you the kind of
回来只是为了向您展示
experience you get this is the kind of
经历你得到的是那种
thing you could do it's it's a pattern
你可以做的事情是一种模式
that you'll find in boot a lot so
您会在启动中找到很多
whenever you want to customize something
每当你想定制东西
we will provide customizer callback api
我们将提供定制程序回调API
for that so if you the same thing as a
为此，如果您与
principal extractor really if you
真正的主要提取者
implement a bin of principle extractor
实现原理提取器箱
will call you and you'll get a chance to
会打电话给您，您将有机会
return a different user in this case you
在这种情况下，返回其他用户
implement a being of type J cache
实现J型缓存的存在
manager customizer and before the
经理定制器以及
application start servicing requests we
应用程序开始服务请求，我们
will give you the cache manager and
将为您提供缓存管理器和
you'll get a chance to tune it any way
您将有机会以任何方式对其进行调整
you like
你喜欢
so in this case I'm creating three
所以在这种情况下，我要创建三个
caches and I'm using the GSI API to
缓存，我正在使用GSI API
basically say I want to enable
基本上说我想启用
statistics I want to this one to expire
我希望这个统计数据过期
the entries expire after 10 minutes
条目将在10分钟后过期
stuff like that so we've created three
这样的东西，所以我们创建了三个
cache names one for the calm
缓存名称以保持冷静
today's game is one for the latest
今天的比赛是最新的
polish commits because we have that sign
波兰承诺，因为我们有那个迹象
saying with where when the lash last
说什么时候睫毛持续
polish commits will happen on on our
波兰人的承诺将在我们身上发生
projects and as well another cash name
项目以及另一个现金名称
for the user information we're
对于用户信息，我们是
attracting so we we are basically using
吸引，所以我们基本上是在使用
that data method when you intend to gate
您打算选通时使用的数据方法
to retrieve more information about you
检索有关您的更多信息
right so if I do this well as you would
对，所以如果我做得很好，
expect it works problem next up is we
期待它下一个问题是我们
want to we want to we've been developing
想要我们想要我们一直在发展
this app we've been changing many things
这个应用程序我们一直在改变很多事情
but I think maybe it's about time that
但我认为也许是时候了
we have some kind of better management
我们有更好的管理
of the schema so we haven't seen so much
模式的，所以我们没有看到太多
about the database of our it's an h2
关于我们的数据库是h2
database in memory we don't care about
我们不在乎的内存中的数据库
the schema it's created automatically by
由它自动创建的模式
hibernate we don't know what kind of
冬眠，我们不知道是什么样的
what kind of DDL hibernate is using but
休眠使用哪种DDL，但是
we would like to have more control over
我们希望对
the schema and better yet if we want to
模式，更好的是，如果我们想
have a persistent database instead with
有一个持久数据库而不是
some data and want to change the schema
一些数据并想要更改架构
because we want to add more feature
因为我们想添加更多功能
store more data we want an easy way to
存储更多数据，我们想要一种简单的方法
actually upgrade that schema okay what
实际升级该架构好吗
we want basically is whenever we deploy
我们想要的基本上是每当我们部署
a new version of our application we want
我们想要的应用程序的新版本
the schema to update automatically so
模式会自动更新，因此
the first thing we need to do really is
我们真正要做的第一件事是
to use a schema manager and there is
使用模式管理器，有
actually a couple of ones you can use
实际上可以使用几个
there is liquid base and flyweight so
有液体基料和飞重物，所以
we're going to use a flyweight for this
我们将为此使用飞重
one so I'm adding the dependency as
一个，所以我将依赖项添加为
you'll find with boot that's pretty much
您会发现启动时几乎没有
something that consistent whenever you
每当你保持一致的东西
add more dependencies boot will detect
添加更多依赖项引导将检测
them and do something by default for you
他们，并默认为您做点什么
so the way it works with flyweight is
所以它与flyweight一起工作的方式是
you need to create a directory as
您需要创建一个目录为
directory structure sorry called DB
目录结构对不起叫DB
migration so
因此迁移
yeah and that folder should hold all the
是的，那个文件夹应该容纳所有
sequel scripts that are that should be
应该是的续集脚本
used to create your database and to
用于创建数据库并
adapt it and modify it for the newest
对其进行修改并对其进行最新修改
versions whenever you decide you need to
决定何时需要版本
change something in your database so as
更改数据库中的内容，以便
long as you're respecting the the
只要您尊重
conventions with the version underscore
版本下划线的约定
underscore the name of the the schema
强调模式名称
you're trying to to apply that sequel as
您正在尝试将该续集应用为
long as you adopt that that convention
只要您采用该约定
you're good to go
你很好走
so here for the first version of our
所以这里是我们的第一个版本
database we're deciding to create our
我们正在决定创建数据库
tables with the submissions and our
提交内容和我们的表格
users but still since we're doing that
用户，但仍然是因为我们正在这样做
we don't need to we don't need hibernate
我们不需要休眠
to do that for us anymore right so we
再为我们做到这一点，所以我们
kind of need to disable that so we're
需要禁用它，所以我们
going to tell having it yeah
会告诉你有
don't Milo - yeah okay so that's by the
别Milo-是的，好的，那是在
way that's a good example of
这是一个很好的例子
auto-completion for values you can see
自动完成您可以看到的值
the thing on the right you're wondering
你想知道的右边的东西
right now can I do that for my own keys
现在我可以用自己的钥匙来做吗
yes you can do that and it's actually
是的，你可以做到，实际上
very easy and if you have a menu so if
非常简单，如果您有菜单，那么如果
you expose an a new type you'll get that
你暴露出一种新的类型，你会得到
total completion out of the box and
开箱即用的总完成时间，
we'll fetch well we don't the good IDE
我们会获取不好的东西，我们不好的IDE
developers do that for us they will
开发人员为我们做到这一点，他们将
fetch the Javadoc
取得Javadoc
on the enemy and will display that right
对敌人，并显示该权利
there so I'm going to say none and let's
在那里，我不会说什么，让我们
see what happens if I restart yep that's
看看如果我重新启动是怎么回事
not very funny at this point because
在这一点上还不是很有趣，因为
we're still using an in-memory database
我们仍在使用内存数据库
right so don't really care just to prove
对，所以真的不在乎只是证明
that our application still works yeah
我们的应用程序仍然有效
but still since we're using flyweight we
但是仍然因为我们使用的是飞重
want to make sure that one the the
要确保一个
tables are created properly in our
在我们的表中正确创建表
database and that or database is still
数据库并且那个或数据库仍然
working so when you create a submission
在创建提交时工作正常
it still works
它仍然有效
when we take a look at the actual h2
当我们看一下实际的h2
console and for our in memory database
控制台和我们的内存数据库
we can see that not only we have our
我们可以看到，不仅我们拥有
submission user tables we also have a
提交用户表，我们还有一个
new
新
schema version table that lists all the
架构版本表，其中列出了所有
the actual scripts that are applied
实际应用的脚本
against your database whenever migration
每当迁移时都对数据库
occurs and we can also get that
发生，我们也可以得到
information from a separate end point
来自单独端点的信息
that are that is provided by spring
春天提供的
boots where you can see in a nice JSON
可以在漂亮的JSON中看到的靴子
format the only migration that are
格式化唯一的迁移
applied through database so instead of
通过数据库应用，因此而不是
going to your table and seeing what
去桌旁看看
migrations have been applied you can
迁移已应用，您可以
check that information directly with the
直接与
with that end point if you happen to
与那个终点，如果你碰巧
prefer liquid base you'll get exactly
更喜欢液体基料，您将得到
the same features so you have an ad
相同的功能，所以您有一个广告
where it's I mean because we do critic
我的意思是因为我们批评家
we redirect it but you have a liquid
我们重定向它，但是你有液体
base endpoint that gives liquid based
基础端点，提供液体
information about your schema so that's
有关您的架构的信息，因此
very convenient but let's maybe switch
非常方便，但让我们切换一下
to a real database so what we want to
到一个真实的数据库，所以我们想要
show you is how you can easily change
告诉你如何轻松改变
the environment locally and use ID
本地环境并使用ID
settings ID feature to do so so one
设置ID功能就可以做到这一点
thing I want to do now is I want to
我现在想做的是
connect to my local my sequel database
连接到本地我的续集数据库
so I have it here and if you look that I
所以我在这里，如果你看我
have a CFP I have a CFP database and
有一个CFP，我有一个CFP数据库，
there is actually no tables in there
那里实际上没有桌子
okay
好的
so let's switch to my secret so what
所以让我们切换到我的秘密
does it take to switch from h2 to my
从h2切换到我的
sequin and make that configurable the
亮片并使其可配置
first thing is we want to create a file
首先是我们要创建一个文件
a profile and that's very small and call
个人资料，它很小，可以致电
that local okay so application - local
该本地还可以，所以应用程序-本地
is going to be loaded if the local
如果本地将要加载
profile is active it's some kind of
个人资料已启用，这是某种
convention input and I'm going to say
约定输入，我要说的是
you all know my password now but it only
你们现在都知道我的密码，但只有
applies to localhost huh
适用于localhost呵呵
so this is the settings that you have to
所以这是你必须要做的设置
do you may notice that you're not
你可能会注意到你不是
specifying the driver you don't have to
指定不需要的驱动程序
there's plenty of samples on the
上面有很多样本
internet explaining how you can connect
互联网解释如何连接
spring boot to a database and 99% of
spring boot 到数据库和99％的
them have the driver don't
他们有司机没有
that because we actually extract the
那是因为我们实际上提取了
driver for you from the real you are
真正的驱动力
right
对
so it's an information you don't have to
所以这是您不需要的信息
provide but you still need to provide
提供，但您仍然需要提供
the actual driver somewhere like us
像我们这样的地方的真正司机
becomes do that for you for you so you
成为为你做的，所以你
need to go back to your pond and add
需要回到你的池塘并添加
that as a dependency properly so nice
作为依赖关系很好
aquarium right so now that we have the
水族馆吧，现在我们有了
driver we have the local configuration
驱动程序，我们有本地配置
we still need to trigger that actual
我们仍然需要触发实际
local profile in our application so the
应用程序中的本地配置文件，因此
next step if you want to keep both
如果要同时保留两个
environments so you want to keep the h2
环境，所以您要保持h2
in memory database and whatever you want
在内存数据库中以及您想要的任何内容
and do the data every time you listen
并在每次收听时进行数据处理
you stop the app or you want to connect
您停止应用程序或要连接
to physical database then the good way
到物理数据库的好方法
to do that in the IDS service well
在IDS服务中做到这一点
actually you have to run configuration
实际上，您必须运行配置
for that there is the same feature in
为此，它具有相同的功能
SES so I'm going to clone the run config
SES，所以我要克隆运行配置
I'm going to call that whatever you
我不管你怎么称呼
could go that my sequel or whatever you
可以去我的续集或任何你
want and right here I'm going to say I
想要，就在这里我要说我
want to enable the local profile okay so
想启用本地配置文件
the only the only difference between the
唯一的区别是
two is that one is enabling the local
二是一个使本地
profiles that will read that thing and
将读取该内容的配置文件，以及
the other one won't so if I'm starting
另一个不会，如果我要开始
the app now is the local profile and i
该应用程序现在是本地配置文件，而我
refresh right here I'll have my tables
在这里刷新我要整理桌子
created for me okay so that's all all
为我创建好了，就这些
the already takes to connect to a
已经需要连接到
different database you just provide
您刚刚提供的其他数据库
those three properties because you do so
这三个属性，因为您这样做
you're actually telling spring boot okay
你实际上是在告诉 spring boot 好吗
there is a ch2 there so you could create
那里有一个ch2，所以您可以创建
on h2 database in memory but I'm telling
在内存中的H2数据库上，但我告诉
you this is where the database is
您这是数据库所在的位置
located for my app so you have you're
为我的应用程序定位，因此您拥有
basically having an opinion in
基本上有意见
configuration we will detect that and
配置，我们将检测到并
you will use that information to create
您将使用该信息来创建
the data source for you yeah so we can
是您的数据源，所以我们可以
even try to create a few submissions
甚至尝试创建一些提交
within our application it's just to
在我们的应用程序中
prove it works
证明它有效
okay from you a big topic
好的，很重要
so it didn't take that long for us to
所以我们花了很短的时间
change the authentication mechanism rely
改变认证机制依赖
on Olaf handle or database change a few
在Olaf句柄或数据库上更改一些
things in our application that that's
在我们的应用程序中
already a lot of features in just a few
在少数几个中已经有很多功能
minutes and now we're going to see how
分钟，现在我们要看看
we can have even more fun by changing
我们可以通过改变来获得更多的乐趣
our database while the application is in
应用程序在其中时我们的数据库
production holding that or holding data
生产持有或持有数据
and that's the actual thing you want to
这就是您想要的实际内容
do when you're using something like
当您使用类似的东西时
Flyway so let's say that you've done the
飞路，让我们说您已经完成了
first release of this app and you have
该应用的第一个版本，您已经
some data in production results all
生产结果中的一些数据全部
kinds of paper and your customer is
各种纸张，您的客户是
telling you well this form is nice but
告诉你这个表格很好但是
we really need a separate section so
我们真的需要一个单独的部分
that the the speaker could add notes to
演讲者可以在其中添加注释
the CFP so some information about why am
CFP，所以一些关于为什么要
I submitting that talk what I'm going to
我把那个演讲提交给我
do some basically information that needs
做一些基本的信息
to be exchanged between the CFP in this
在此之间CFP之间进行交换
feature so um it's very convenient now
功能，所以它现在非常方便
that we have Flyway is we are going to
我们有Flyway是我们要
add a note attribute to our submission
为我们的提交添加一个注释属性
table and for that I'm going to again do
桌子，为此，我要再次做
that thing yeah so in that commit we are
是的，所以在那个承诺中，我们是
adding a new sequel script a new
添加新的续集脚本
migration script we are adding a new
迁移脚本，我们要添加一个新的
field in our submission form we are
在我们的提交表格中
adding a new field as well in the entry
在条目中也添加一个新字段
domain entry itself and as you can see
域条目本身，如您所见
we've got a new entry in our form and we
我们在表单中有一个新条目，我们
can create a new entry with those notes
可以使用这些注释创建一个新条目
like this
像这样
so now now we've got that we should have
所以现在我们已经有了
right something different in our
对我们的东西有所不同
database yes
数据库是
so also something that you may have
所以你可能也有
noticed is the application was running
注意到应用程序正在运行
right so the application was running I
正确，因此应用程序正在运行
did the checkout of this new comment
结帐了这个新评论
that add more feature it's like I would
增加更多功能就像我会
have coded myself like could have
像可能那样编码自己
probably taken an hour of 30 minutes to
大概花了一个小时30分钟
do so just to add all the funeral
这样做只是为了添加所有葬礼
everything I and I did not have to
我和我不需要做的一切
restart right and bam here's my app
正确重新启动，这是我的应用程序
updated for me with the database updated
为我更新了数据库
for me yes so the question is should you
对我来说，所以问题是你应该
write it should you write that script
写它，如果你写那个脚本
yourself or is there some tool you can
自己还是有一些工具可以
use to generate it for you I'm probably
用于为您生成它，我可能
out I think I don't know if there isn't
我想我不知道是否没有
there's probably an app that does that
可能有一个应用程序可以做到这一点
but I'm more in the camp of if you're
但如果你是
using that stuff you probably want to
使用您可能想要的东西
make to maintain the script and you want
做维护脚本，你想要
to make sure what happens and you may
确保会发生什么，您可能
also want to choose also the database
也想选择数据库
according to what you're using there
根据您在那里使用的
might be some things in my sequel
可能是我续集中的某些内容
obviously there's not a lot of data here
显然这里没有很多数据
but in a real production application you
但是在实际的生产应用程序中
may want to use some tricks of the
可能想使用一些技巧
database something that are not standard
数据库不标准的东西
and that's where generation tools
这就是生成工具的地方
usually don't provide you that kind of
通常不会为您提供那种
feature and here we're just adding a new
功能，在这里我们只是添加一个新
column in a database but when you use
数据库中的列，但使用时
those tools usually you you rename in
您通常在其中重命名的那些工具
Colin you need to tweak something in
柯林，您需要调整一些内容
existing values like set a set the
现有的值，例如设置一个
default values for for so many entries
许多条目的默认值
etc so you're not just changing this
等等，所以你不只是改变这个
schema usually also doing something very
模式通常也会做一些非常重要的事情
specific to your own domain to change
特定于您自己的域进行更改
things in for all the existing data so
所有现有数据的数据
that's where maybe a tool could do
那也许是一个工具可以做的
things for you but certainly not
东西给你，但肯定不是
everything
一切
so maybe just extracting if you've got
所以如果你有的话，也许只是提取
something already in a database
数据库中已有的东西
somewhere with
与某处
the actual type maybe you can just
实际的类型也许你可以
extract the create table statement but
提取创建表语句，但是
for other things it's probably more
对于其他事情，可能更多
complex you probably want to do that
复杂，您可能想这样做
yourself so what's in this coming
你自己，这是怎么回事
through
通过
yeah right did you get that didn't I
是的，你明白了吗？
didn't get the question so we can do a
没有得到问题，所以我们可以做一个
wiki it's not it's it's GPA right now
Wiki不是它，现在是GPA
running okay so if you look if you look
运行正常，所以如果你看的话
at the I'm not really answering your
在我不是真的回答你
question but we're using GPA were using
问题，但我们正在使用GPA
have an eight so what we've done is we
有八个，所以我们要做的是
we told have an eight please don't
我们告诉了一个八，请不要
generate the schema right but you could
生成模式权限，但是您可以
say please do so and please vlog it then
说请这样做，然后将其博客
you could see in the logs worth having
您可以在日志中看到值得拥有的
it generated and take that as a base
它产生并以此为基础
that's actually what I did because I'm
那实际上是我所做的，因为我
raising so I just did that I copy/paste
提高，所以我只是做了我复制/粘贴
for the first version and once you have
对于第一个版本，一旦
the schema running then you can okay
模式运行就可以了
thank you yeah
谢谢耶
can you speak louder please because
你能大声说话吗，因为
No so the question is I have all those
不，所以问题是我拥有所有这些
databases all those different databases
所有这些不同的数据库
and they may have specific things that
他们可能有一些特定的东西
they support or do not support is there
他们支持还是不支持
a way to have sort of some generic way
一种具有某种通用方式的方式
of ending that that's the question right
结束那就是问题对了
I don't think so
我不这么认为
however what you have is Flyway is you
但是你拥有的是Flyway是你
can have database specific scripts so we
可以有特定于数据库的脚本，所以我们
have this platform thing that you can
有这个平台的东西，你可以
use to fine tune according to the actual
用于根据实际情况进行微调
database type
数据库类型
that's what we've done right that's
那就是我们所做的正确的
exactly what we've done in this app we
正是我们在这个应用程序中所做的
let right right but on the other hand if
让权利吧，但另一方面，如果
you support multiple databases with
您支持多个数据库
advanced kheema a structure that's the
高级风湿病的结构是
price to pay I think yeah that's
要付出的代价，我认为是的
actually what we did for the spring data
实际上我们对 spring data 做了什么
website we created the tables with the
网站上我们创建了带有
JPA etc when we started building the
JPA等，当我们开始构建
application and now that it's running in
应用程序，现在它正在运行
production we have were using flyweight
我们使用飞重的生产
to update the schema and update the data
更新架构并更新数据
as well in production when we are
在生产中
updating the application which is a
更新应用程序是
fairly often so once you've got a lot of
经常这样，一旦你有很多
data in your in your database and you're
您数据库中的数据，并且
not considering changing the database
不考虑更改数据库
and sorry can be pretty useful in those
对不起，在那些情况下
in those cases
在那些情况下
okay so we still have two minutes just
好，所以我们还有两分钟
to recap what we've done right so we had
回顾一下我们正确做的事情，所以我们有了
we had an app we use dev tools to modify
我们有一个应用程序，使用开发工具进行修改
this app we integrate it both and single
这个程序，我们将它集成和单个
sign-on with added caching with added
使用添加的缓存登录
database management you can see now that
您现在可以看到数据库管理
our schema is at version 1.1 so whenever
我们的架构是1.1版
you need to do a change now you are you
你现在需要改变
have all the infrastructure to do so and
有所有的基础设施
we've also configure security in such a
我们还在这种情况下配置了安全性
way that the information we get from
我们从中获取信息的方式
getup is linked to a user table that we
getup链接到我们的用户表
have in our system so I think that's it
在我们的系统中，所以我认为就是这样
we have one minute left so probably a
我们还有一分钟，所以大概
bit too late for questions I'm afraid
我担心的问题有点太晚了
but we are right here if you want thank
但是我们就在这里，如果你想谢谢
you very much thanks
你非常感谢